One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Cross this endless sea with me and search for
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please, following
the footprints of those who pursue their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we put our minds together,
we'll get through it
always
Get running, get running
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Keep chasing, keep chasing
the compass that leads to our dreams
always points straight ahead
We can't stop here
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can take hold of tomorrow
Keep chasing, keep chasing
everything we see in the moment,
we should record it all
the blank slates of our minds
Vital Response
Oh, Franky, I want to tell you something while we have a chance.
Hm?
Then, we can't do anything until we find that No. 2 key?!
Yeah. That's right.
How stupid!
Well, at least I know what's going on.
I'm really angry now!
He sure is tough. He's up now.
Stay there and watch.
Franky...
Destroyer Cannon!
Wow!
Ow, ow, ow! I don't like this attack
because it dislocates my joints!
What?! You shouldn't do it, then!
What a moron.
I'm a Six Powers master.
Cannonballs would never hit me!
No matter how much you run around,
you can't escape from my
Franky Destroyer Cannon...
because it's got homing cannonballs!
Homing cannonballs?!
Could it be that the cannonballs
sense the enemy and follow them?!
I've never heard of such technology!
What the heck is he?
Huh?
Hold it!
So it's you who homes in on the enemy?!
You jerk! Hold it!
I fell for it! That bastard!
He disappeared again.
Where are you hiding?!
It's no use searching for me.
I'm an expert at Shave, one of the Six Powers.
In addition to my lightning speed,
I make no noise when moving about,
just like owls when they hunt.
I execute perfect assassinations.
An owl, huh?
My target won't see me until
the very moment I kill him.
Take this!
He was hiding here.
Looks like that attack caught
you completely off guard, huh?
How impertinent!
I've never experienced such humiliation!
I'm a CP9 assassin!
Shave!
Whoa!
Iron Ball!
Ah! Watch out!
Dammit! We're above the sea!
Franky!
This is terrible!
If he gets swept away...
he'll be headed straight
to the basin of the waterfall!
Since he's in the sea, I can't rescue him.
Franky! Hang in there!
I can use Moon Walk if I get pulled into the waterfall.
This is bad! I can't get out of the undertow!
What a strong current! I can't
keep holding my breath, either!
I have to get to the surface, no matter what!
Sink deeper!
That voice! Don't tell me
he broke the fridge door!
What a feast!
Hold on! He got fatter!
Just how much food in that fridge did you eat?!
I don't wanna drown in a place like this!
Ahhh! I'm almost at the basin of the falls!
I'll die! I'll die! I'm falling! Ahhh!
Franky Butterfly!
I won't let you get away!
Moon Walk!
Tough Dugong!
That bastard!
Weapons Left!
Paper Art!
Slime!
Dammit! What the hell was that?!
Oh, so close!
This is really bad.
I've just gotta get to the shore!
1.0 Cola Cannon! Coup de Boo!
Have you learned your lesson?
It takes more than just strength
to defeat a Six Powers master!
Strong Hammer!
Paper Art.
Fall into the falls!
Strong Right!
What?
What?!
Come with me!
Let go of me, you bastard!
Moon Walk with just one leg
can't support two people!
We're gonna fall!
Yeah, seems like it.
So why don't you bring both of us
back to the shore before we fall?
Or do you wanna try fighting me
while supporting our weight?
I might win,
but my life would be in danger, too.
We're certainly in the same boat.
Take us back to the shore.
Okay! That's right!
Good job, good job.
Let's get back to the shore together.
But it looks like I'll win the fight once we get there!
Oh? You think so?
Yeah, because I just thought of a way
to finish you off with just one blow.
Oh? So did I, Fukuro-kun.
Now, what're you gonna do?
Take me to the shore already
so that I can knock you out!
You don't have to tell me!
I'll shut you up right here, right now!
Super Cartwheel Iron Ball!
I'll slam you into the corner of
the tower using this momentum!
I see. It indeed looks like
I'll get smashed into pieces.
Franky Centaur!
I've got both your legs!
Now you can't move however you want in the air!
So what?! That still can't stop this momentum!
That's not totally true.
70mm 0.2 Cola Cannon!
A bit of Coup de Vent!
Ahh! I lost my momentum!
You stopped the cartwheel! Damn you!
But this is enough!
We're already above the shore!
Now, take this!
70mm 1.5 Max Cola Power!
Coup de...
What're you doing?!
Give up already, you bastard!
Coup de...
Vent!
Super!
Isn't the No. 2 key here yet?
Zoro-kun! This is it for me! I'm exhausted.
Carry me on your back.
Why would I?!
Tempest Kick.
Finger Pistol!
What're you doing?!
You just aimed at me while pretending
to attack those two, didn't you?!
That's a false accusation,
but if you want, we can fight.
I've been frustrated for a while now
that you've been in my way.
What'd you say?! That's what I
wanna say, you stupid herbivore!
No, I'd have to say I prefer meat.
We'll play rock-paper-scissors, Sogeking.
– What?
– The problem is these handcuffs.
There's a way to get them off of us.
I'll cut off the hand of the loser.
Wh-What's with you coming up with
such a scary idea looking so serious?!
I'm not done! Keep listening!
So the one who gets the handcuffs off like that...
will hurry to Chopper with their cut-off hand...
and have Chopper reconnect it to their wrist!
We're not stuffed animals! Don't be ridiculous!
I've got another idea.
Ahh! Ahh! I don't wanna hear it!
I'm tired of arguing.
I can start anytime. The winner can
keep the prey all to himself.
– Hm?
– What's that?
Listen, Sogeking. Don't lose your posture.
You are a sword!
Someone get me a lawyer! I'll sue you for sure!
I've never seen anyone with
as little self-discipline as him.
I can't believe he gained that much weight in just a few minutes alone.
You don't... need to be...
need to be... need to be...
I'm not concerned! Just speak normally!
That's “need to be concerned”, right?!
Thank you!
That's exactly what I was... I was... I was...
I got it, so you can cut that out!
Anyway, there's no need
to be concerned, then?
Come back here!
I was... I was... That's right!
As for why,
just watch!
Vital Response!
Wh-What the heck?!
Digest!
Absorb!
Now, I'm back to normal!
Ahhh! What?! What are you?!
What did you just do?!
Do it again.
Vital Response!
Digest!
Absorb!
You're amazing! How does that work?!
Glad you asked!
A thousand years at sea, and a
thousand years in the mountains...
Breathing in the wind and drinking dewdrops,
I trained myself, living as a hermit!
After all that, I've... I've... I've...
I've acquired this “Vital Response”!
Essentially, if you extend
your consciousness everywhere,
from your hair to your internal organs,
toes, even the tip of your downy hair,
there's no part of your body
that you can't manipulate.
Extending your consciousness
even to the tip of your hair?
I've read about that kind
of ability in a book before.
It's called something like biofeedback.
Then your hair moves around like
an octopus because of that ability?!
An octopus?! How terribly rude!
Call me... a valiant...
lion... will... will you?!
Why does it matter which one?
Vital Response!
Hair Bind!
Dammit!
If those catch me, I'm done for!
Shave!
Where did he go?!
Finger Pistol: Cue!
That stick doesn't even have a pointed tip!
Cue! Cue! Cue!
Heavy Gong!
Iron Body!
Ow, ow, ow!
What's the matter?!
Dammit!
As I thought, he won't budge unless
I attack with Arm Point or Horn Point.
But rumble balls are potent drugs.
The proper dosage is one every six hours.
If I take more than that,
it'll be a huge strain on my body.
Plus, the second one will
alter the transformation wavelength,
and so it'll be hard to
control my transformations.
With the third one, I'll lose consciousness
and hardly be able to fight.
What do I do? I could get stronger if I just take one more.
I'll roast you on a skewer!
Shishi Kebab!
I'm just wasting time like this!
Rumble!
The risk is high, but I have a chance!
It's now all or nothing!
I'll somehow finish this within three minutes!
Take this!
Horn Point!
What?!
Wrong one!
Ow, ow, ow!
Kebab!
Jumping Point!
Ah! Wrong one!
As I feared, I can't control
my transformations. Dammit!
If only I could somehow use Arm Point,
I could hit him with a full-powered Cloven attack!
The fire is spreading, making this room more dangerous.
This is no time for me to be stuck
with a guy with no key on him!
I'd better hurry up and get the No. 2 key...
and free Zoro and Sogeking!
Or we can't rescue Robin!
That's right! Robin!
That's right! I'm...
I'm...
I'm fighting in order to save our friend!
What a tough animal!
Vital Response!
His hair took the form of hands!
I have to do it! I can't be
defeated in a place like this!
I'm their only hope!
Shishi Finger Pistol!